Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio Materials, 1953-2000; undated; 2
  - Mobilink radio spots, 1993 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-164)
  - Mobilink 9 radio spots, 1993 (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-165)
  - NBC--50th Anniversary 3-4, Undated (Box A3, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-166)
  - NBC--50th Anniversary 5, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-167)
  - NBC--50th Anniversary Sy Oliver WNEW, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-168)
  - NBC--The First Fabulous 50 parts 1-2, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-169)
  - NBC--The First Fabulous 50 parts 3-4, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-170)
  - Nestle/Davide Sunflower Seeds--Good Times Female, 1996 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-171)
  - Paramount Home Video--Days of Thunder radio, 1990 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-172)
  - Presentation to New York Society of Security Analysts, 1978 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-173)
  - Presentation to New York Society of Security Analysts, 1978 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-174)
  - Press Conference, Consumer Food Council, 1977 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-175)
  - Press Conference, Consumer Food Council, 1977 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-176)
  - Stan Freberg radio spots, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-177)
  - Standard Brands--Radio spots, 1990 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-178)
  - Standard Brands--3 spots tied, 1989 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-179)
  - Standard Brands--Paint Co. After/Inspired, 1988 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-180)
  - Standard Brands--Paint Co. Living Room, 1988 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-181)
  - Standard Brands--Family Room, 1988 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-182)
  - Standard Brands--Paint Co. Ka-Bloom, 1990 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-183)
  - Standard Brands--Paint Co. 4x60 radio, 1990 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-184)
  - Standard Brands--Trust Me, 1989 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-185)
  - Supercuts--5 radio spots, 1991 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-186)
  - Supercuts--Annette/Beverly, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-187)
  - Supercuts--Grand Rapids region radio, 1992 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-188)
  - Supercuts--NFL promo, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-189)
  - Supercuts--NFL promo, 1991 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-190)
  - Supercuts--Olympics promo, 1992 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-191)
  - Supercuts--Pony Tale/Tricky Spot/Cowabunga, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-192)
  - Supercuts--Stylabration, 1992 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-193)
  - Supercuts--Style II, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-194)
  - Supercuts--Supercut II, 1992 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-195)
  - Supercuts--Supertrains campaign, Undated (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-196)
  - Supercuts--Terry Leonard/Troy Martinez, 1992 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-197)
  - Supercuts--Troy Martinez, 1992 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-198)
  - Summertime Blues 3x30, 1987 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-199)
  - Tempositions radio 5x60, 1996 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-200)
  - United Foundation radio, 1986 (Box A4, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-201)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Augusto DeAngelo, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-202)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Burt Manning, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-203)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Denis Lanigan, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-204)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Denis Lanigan, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-205)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Johnston, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-206)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Johnston, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-207)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Johnston tape 2, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-208)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Robertson, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-209)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Robertson, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-210)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Thompson, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-211)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Don Thompson, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-212)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 1, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-213)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 1, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-214)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 2, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-215)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 2, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-216)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 3, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-217)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 3, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-218)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 4, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-219)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Harry Clark 4, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-220)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Hugh Connell, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-221)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Jack Cronin, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-222)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Jack Cronin, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-223)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Jack Cronin, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-224)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Jack Webster, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-225)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Jack Webster, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-226)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Jack Webster tape 2, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-227)
  - JWT Oral History Project--John Monserrat, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-228)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Leon Hontiveros, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-229)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Leon Hontiveros, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-230)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Norm Varney tape 2, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-231)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Norm Varney tape 1, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-232)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Norm Varney, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-233)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Norm Varney tape 2, 1994 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-234)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Rai Senior tape 1, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-235)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Rai Senior tape 1, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-236)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Rai Senior tape 2, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-237)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Rai Senior tape 2, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-238)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Rai Senior tape 3, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-239)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Rai Senior tape 3, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-240)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Ted Wilson, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-241)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Ted Wilson, 1991 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-242)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Tom Sutton tape 1, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-243)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Tom Sutton tape 1, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-244)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Tom Sutton tape 1, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-245)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Tom Sutton tape 2, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-246)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Tom Sutton tape 2, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-247)
  - JWT Oral History Project--Tom Sutton tape 3, 1990 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-248)
  - JWT Oral History Project--W. Lee Preschel tape 1, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-249)
  - JWT Oral History Project--W. Lee Preschel tape 2, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-250)
  - JWT Oral History Project--W. Lee Preschel tape 3, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-251)
  - JWT Oral History Project--W. Lee Preschel tape 4, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-252)
  - JWT Oral History Project--W. Lee Preschel tape 5, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-253)
  - JWT Oral History Project--W. Lee Preschel tape 6, 1992 (Box A5, Audio-cassette RL00734-CS-254)
  - Bailey's--Bailey's Sweepstakes; original mastser, 1999 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-001)
  - Bailey's--Bailey's Sweepstakes; session tape, 1999 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-002)
  - Chevron/Ortho Weed-B-Gon--Roses/Lawn voiceover, 1993-1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-003)
  - Ford F-Series--"Ashley" voices only session tape, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-004)
  - iPlanet.com radio--Hold Your Hand original master, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-005)
  - iPlanet.com radio--Hold Your Hand/Options original master, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-006)
  - iPlanet.com radio--Hold Your Hand/Options session tape 1, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-007)
  - iPlanet.com radio--Hold Your Hand/Options session tape 2, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-008)
  - Ivomec--Lice-Free Guarantee, 1999 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-009)
  - Ivomec--Lice-Free Guarantee original master (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-010)
  - Ivomec--Lice-Free Guarantee session tape (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-011)
  - Ivomec--Weatherman/Brothers original master, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-012)
  - Ivomec--Weatherman/Brothers session tape, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-013)
  - JWT Christmas Chorus, 1966 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-014)
  - Kodak--Artist, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-015)
  - Kodak--Auction, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-016)
  - Kodak--Clayton Crayon Company, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-017)
  - Kodak--Evidence, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-018)
  - Kodak--Beach, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-019)
  - Kodak--Bird, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-020)
  - Kodak--Cruise/Risk, 1993 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-021)
  - Kodak/Goldmax--Frankville/Wedding Advice/Rebel/Theater, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-022)
  - Kodak/Lost World--I'm Wrong, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-023)
  - Kodak--Sounds Local, 1993 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-024)
  - Kodak--Tour Bus, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-025)
  - Kodak--Tour Bus, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-026)
  - Kodak/Goldmax--Whatever, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-027)
  - Kraft/Nabisco--Party production tape, 2006 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-028)
  - Lipton Ice Tea--8 spots safety copy, 2001 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-029)
  - Lipton--Cool vs. Brisk :60, 1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-030)
  - Lipton--Cool vs. Brisk :40, 1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-031)
  - Lipton--Like Shake/Well Spoken/Shaking 3x:60, Undated (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-032)
  - Lipton--Like Shake/Well Spoken/Shaking 3x:40, Undated (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-033)
  - Lipton Bottle Mix--Magic Potion Bottle, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-034)
  - Lipton Brisk--Press Conference :40, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-035)
  - Lipton Brew--3 spots, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-036)
  - Lipton Brew--9 spots, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-037)
  - Lipton Brew--6 spots, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-038)
  - Lipton Brew--9 spots, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-039)
  - Lipton Brisk--Cafeteria promo Frank Sinatra, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-040)
  - Lipton Brisk Can--Tastes Great, 1998 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-041)
  - Lipton Brisk Sweetened--Tastes Great Sweetened, 1998 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-042)
  - Lipton Brisk--radio Whirlpool/Tastes Great, 1998 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-043)
  - Lipton Brisk--TV Birthday/Moving, 1998 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-044)
  - Lipton Brisk--radio Whirlpool/Diet, 1998 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-045)
  - Listerine--13 spots session tape voiceover 1, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-046)
  - Listerine--13 spots session tape voiceover 2, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-047)
  - Listerine--13 spots transfer tape, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-048)
  - Pepsi/Lipton's Iced Tea--Fun Day, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-049)
  - Pepsi/Lipton's Iced Tea--Girlfriend, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-050)
  - Pepsi/Lipton's Iced Tea--Roommate, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-051)
  - Pepsi/Lipton's Iced Tea--4 spots :60, 2000 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-052)
  - Rolaids--Bad Call, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-053)
  - Rolaids--Bad Call original master, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-054)
  - Rolaids--Bad Call 1:1 safety copy, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-055)
  - Rolaids--Bad Call voiceovers, 1997 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-056)
  - Society Bank session tape, 1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-057)
  - Society Bank--Echoes/Near and Far safety copy, 1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-058)
  - Society Bank--New Roof/House Money original master, 1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-059)
  - Society Bank--New Roof/House Money session tape, 1994 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-060)
  - Trident--Radio Lifestyles/Litany, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-061)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Worker Litany original master, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-062)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Worker Litany original master "DNU", 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-063)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Worker Litany session tape voices, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-064)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Worker Litany production master music, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-065)
  - Trident/Listerine--Lifestyles original master, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-066)
  - Trident/Listerine--Lifestyles production master, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-067)
  - Trident--Lifestyle/Worker voice only, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-068)
  - Trident--Wild Radio Line Re-read takes 32-40, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-069)
  - Trident Radio--Worker :30, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-070)
  - Weight Watchers--This Time, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-071)
  - Weight Watchers original master, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-072)
  - Weight Watchers L.A. Radio original master, 1996 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-073)
  - Weight Watchers--Goals/Excuses, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-074)
  - Weight Watchers--Goals/Excuses voice onlyl, 1995 (Box A6, Audio-cassette RL00734-DAT-075)
  - Bailey's--Bailey's Sweepstakes, 1999 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-001)
  - iPlanet--Hold Your Hand, 2000 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-002)
  - iPlanet--Hold Your Hand/Options, 2000 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-003)
  - Ivomec--Lice Free Guarantee, 1999 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-004)
  - Ivomec--Weatherman/Brothers, 2000 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-005)
  - Listerine--13 spots, 2000 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-006)
  - Rolaids--Bad Call, 1997 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-007)
  - Rolaids--Bad Call, 1997 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-008)
  - Society Bank--Echoes/Near and Far, 1994 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-009)
  - Society Bank--New Roof/House Money, 1994 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-010)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Litany, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-011)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Litany audio mastering, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-012)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Litany, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-013)
  - Trident--Lifestyles/Litany, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-014)
  - Trident--Lifestyles, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-015)
  - Trident--Worker, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-016)
  - Trident--Worker safety backup, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-017)
  - Weight Watchers--L.A. Radio rev., 1996 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-018)
  - Weight Watchers--Goals/Excuses revisions, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-019)
  - Weight Watchers--L.A. Radio rev., 1996 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-020)
  - Weight Watchers New Biz--This Time, 1995 (Box A7, Audio-cassette RL00734-D8-021)
  - Alun Jones, Don Johnston; Security Analysts Meeting, 1977 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-001)
  - Arno Johnson, The Little Things, 1965 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-002)
  - Austin MacCormick, U.S. Penal System and the Arkansas Prison Scandal, 1968 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-003)
  - B. Eastwright, Bob and Ray Go to the Conventions, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-004)
  - Bernard Owett, Page Procter, The Creative of a Creative Group, 1968 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-005)
  - Bill Ross, Where I See It Going, Advanced Professional Seminar, 1977 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-006)
  - Chase Manhattan New Business Presentation, 1974 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-007)
  - Dan Seymour, Kick Off Address, Eyes on Thompson, 1966 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-008)
  - Dan Seymour, The New Reality of Radio, 1967 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-009)
  - Dan Seymour, Sidney Bernstein for Ad Age, 1964 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-010)
  - Dick Jones, Media Goes Creative, 1969 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-011)
  - Don Johnston, JWT Europe, 1970 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-012)
  - Edward Robinson, Developing the Proposition, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-013)
  - Frank Anton, Deadline: The Anatomy of an Ad, 1961 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-014)
  - Fred Ronai, New Product Presentation on Ron Rico Rum, 1967 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-015)
  - Georgia Demarest, William Timm, Personnel, 1963 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-016)
  - Granger Tripp, Hard Working Commericlals, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-017)
  - H.J. Barnum, Deltakos, Eyes on Thompson, 1969 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-018)
  - Harry Clark, Columbia College, JWT Worldwide Overview, 1977 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-019)
  - Helen Klintrup, Marie Cary, Wilson Seibert, Larry D'Aloise, Editorial Roundup, Undated (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-020)
  - Henry Schachte, The Changing World of JWT, 1968 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-021)
  - Howard Henderson, The Past as Key to the Future, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-022)
  - Howland Sargeant, Radio Liberty Committee, 1965 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-023)
  - Hugh Connell, B. Hacket, Legal Department in Advertising, 1969 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-024)
  - Hugh Connell remarks to New York Office VPs re Responsibilities under SEC Act of 1934, 1969 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-025)
  - Hugh Parker, The Corporate Image, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-026)
  - JWT Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1976 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-027)
  - JWT Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1973 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-028)
  - JWT Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1973 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-029)
  - J. Walter Thompson Great Adventure, 1993 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-030)
  - James Webb Young, Agency Compensation, 1957 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-031)
  - James Webb Young, How to Become an Advertising Man, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-032)
  - James Webb Young, How to Become an Advertising Man, 1960 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-033)
  - James Webb Young, I Knew J. Walter Thompson, 1962 (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-034)
  - James Webb Young, Tape from 1961 film (Box A8, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-035)
  - James Webb Young, Dick Jones, Opening of Media Seminar, 1960 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-036)
  - John H. Johnson (publisher, Ebony) JWT Seminar, 1966 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-037)
  - John Rost, Publicity in the Marketplace, 1960 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-038)
  - Ken Hinks, Who Was Who at JWT, 1968 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-039)
  - Mal Remington panel, 1961 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-040)
  - Martin Stern, Good Morning, Madam", 1967 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-041)
  - Meredith Conley, Kodak Project 13, 1963 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-042)
  - No, No, Mygatt (Phil Mygatt), Undated (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-043)
  - Norman Strouse, Focus on Careers, 1961 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-044)
  - Norman Strouse, Introduction Art Koponen, History of JWT, 1961 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-045)
  - O'Neill Ryan, Undated (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-046)
  - O'Neill Ryan, Undated (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-047)
  - Pan American, London interview transfer from 35mm, 1963 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-048)
  - Peter Dunham, International, 1960 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-049)
  - Phil Mygatt, JWT TV Workshop, 1960 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-050)
  - Phil Mygatt, Bernard Owett, Ruth Downing, B. McKinney, Creative Teamwork, 1965 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-051)
  - Phil Mygatt, Nan Findlow, Ted Maloney (Australia), Editorial Department, 1962 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-052)
  - Phil Mygatt, Ruth Downing, Harriet Rex, Joyce Noble, Ladies' Day, 1961 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-053)
  - Ralph Hatas and others, National Water Institute, 1961 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-054)
  - Rena Bartos, Undated (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-055)
  - Rena Bartos, Creative Seminar, 1972 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-056)
  - Rena Bartos, Marine Corps Group Session, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-057)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-058)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-059)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session 12:00-2:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-060)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session 12:00-2:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-061)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session 12:00-2:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-062)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session 2:30-5:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-063)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session 2:30-5:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-064)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women Group Session 2:30-5:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-065)
  - Rena Bartos, Working Women, JWT Professional Women 3:30-5:00, 1973 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-066)
  - Robert Buchanan, The Business End of Show Business: Broadcasting, 1963 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-067)
  - Robert Buchanan, TV Programming, 1960 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-068)
  - Robert Colwell, A Venusian View of Advertising, 1964 (Box A9, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-069)
  - Robert Colwell, 1992: A Venusian View of Madison Avenue, 1960 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-070)
  - Robert L. Edens, Eyes on Thompson, 1969 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-071)
  - Sam Meek speech at Yale, 1959 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-072)
  - Sanford S. Parker (Chief Economist, Fortune Magazine), Business Outlook 1968, Men's Luncheon Speaker Forum (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-073)
  - Security Analysts Meeting tape 1, 1978 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-074)
  - Security Analysts Meeting tape 2, 1978 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-075)
  - Seminar in Creative Strategy session 1, What Is a Representative?, 1966 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-076)
  - Seminar in Creative Strategy session 2, Thompson T-Square, 1966 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-077)
  - Seminar in Creative Strategy session 4, How to Make and Sell an Ad, 1966 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-078)
  - Seminar in Creative Strategy session 7, How to "Rule" an Ad to Death, 1966 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-079)
  - Sharmin-Fortinberry, Tarrytown Seminar, 1972 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-080)
  - Sharmin-Fortinberry, Tarrytown Seminar, 1972 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-081)
  - Sidney Bernstein, Historical Highlights, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-082)